http://www.decksdirect.com/privacy

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Last Updated: January 1, 2020
This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using this site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information we provide will be used.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information such as names, postal addresses, email addresses, and so on, when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. Your information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company without your consent, except as stated below or for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
What We Collect:
1. Information you give us about yourself. We collect and store information you provide through our website and over the phone. The information we collect from you includes things like:
Name
Mailing address
Email address
Phone number
Credit card number and other payment information
2. Information collected automatically online. We collect information about your interactions with us, including the type of device or browser you're using, your IP address, your browsing behavior while on our website, and the URLs of the websites you were at before you visited our site (these are called "referring URLs").
DecksDirect and our partners use technologies such as cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.
We may permit third-party service providers to collect and process some information from our digital properties. We may share personal information with those providers and may have similar arrangements with interest-based advertisers.
3. Location information. Some of our digital properties may collect your location. We also may use this information to determine whether to provide you with content, information, and notices that may be required by law based on your location.
Reviews and other content you provide. Our websites and social media pages offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums. Be aware that anyone who accesses these areas may read, collect, and use the information you provide.
How We Use the Info:
Identifying you on our website in order to customize your experience (for example, based on your purchase history or your location)
Fulfilling orders and requests for products, services, or information
Processing refunds, returns, and exchanges
Tracking and confirming online orders
Delivering products to you or others
Marketing and advertising products and services
Conducting research and analysis
Responding to your questions and requests
Improving our products and services
Analyzing website and device application trends and customers interests
Preventing losses and ensuring security
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Retention
We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
The site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Internet Based Advertising
You can opt out of interest-based advertising from third-party providers who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising at www.aboutads.info/choices.
California Consumer Privacy Rights
To exercise the California Consumer Privacy Rights, please email ccpa@decksdirect.com or
call 1-888-824-5316.
The California Consumer Privacy Act provides that California residents may (subject to certain limitations) request the personal information we collect about them as well as ask that we delete the personal information we collect about them. If you are a California resident and have an established business relationship with us, you can request a notice disclosing the categories of personal information we have collected once per calendar year.
To learn more about your California privacy rights, visit our Privacy Notice for California Residents at decksdirect.com/ccpa
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
DecksDirect
DeckingShop by BrandTrex DeckingDuraLife DeckingFiberon DeckingDeckorators DeckingShop By MaterialComposite Decking BoardsPVC DeckingShop By ColorGray DeckingBrown DeckingTan DeckingRed DeckingDeck Tiles & PaversHardwood Deck TilesAZEK PaversBison Porcelain PaversDeck Pedestals & SupportsBison Deck SupportsMRP Deck SupportsDeck InstallationDeck LightingLED Deck LightsLED Post CapsLED Rail LightingLED Stair LightingSolar Deck LightingSolar Post LightsSolar Rail LightingPost Cap LightingLow Voltage Post CapsSolar Post CapsDeck Rail LightingPost Mount / Side MountDeck Rail LightingSolar Deck Rail LightsStep Lights & Stair LightsRecessed Deck Stair LightingUnder Tread LightingPower SuppliesTransformersDimmersTimersWire & WiringSolar BatteriesBulbsLED Replacement BulbsIncandescent BulbsBalustersBaluster StylesFace-Mount Deck BalustersRound BalustersSquare BalustersGlass BalustersStyled BalustersBaluster ConnectorsRound ConnectorsSquare ConnectorsGlass ConnectorsBaluster AccessoriesCollarsBasketsCenterpiecesTouch-Up PaintReplacement PartsDeck Railing ConnectorsLevel Rail ConnectorsStair Rail ConnectorsPost Base AnchorsPost Skirts & TrimRailing SystemsMetal RailingCable RailingGlass Deck RailingComposite Deck RailingsWood RailingDeck Post CapsMetal Fence Post CapsAluminum Post CapsStainless Steel & Copper Post CapsWood Base Post CapsLow Voltage Post CapsMetal Low Voltage Post CapsComposite & Vinyl Low Voltage Post CapsWood Post CapsCedar & Pressure Treated Post CapsHardwood Post CapsMetal Top Wood Post CapsPlastic Top Wood Post CapsSolar Post Cap LightsMetal Solar Post CapsComposite & Vinyl Solar Post CapsWood Solar Post CapsPost Cap BrandsAcorn Deck Products Post CapsAurora Post CapsDeckorators Post CapsDekor Post CapsLMT Mercer Group Post CapsWoodway Post CapsPopular Post Cap Sizes4 X 4 Post Caps6 x 6 Post Caps4 x 6 Post CapsComposite & Vinyl Post CapsPost SkirtsPost Cap AccessoriesScrews & FastenersHidden Deck FastenersCAMO FastenersAZEK TimberTech FastenersTrex FastenersTiger Claw FastenersIPE ClipEBTY Hidden Deck Fastener by Simpson Strong-TieMantis FastenersDeckorators Hidden FastenersFiberon Hidden FastenersShop All Hidden FastenersPlugs & Plug SystemsAZEK Decking PlugsHardwood PlugsTimberTech Decking PlugsTrex Decking PlugsFiberon Decking PlugsOther Decking PlugsDeck ScrewsWood Deck ScrewsComposite Deck ScrewsFlat Head Deck ScrewsTrim Head Deck ScrewsStainless Steel Deck ScrewsMetal Framing ScrewsCollated Deck ScrewsFascia ScrewsReplacement HardwareAccessoriesConcrete & Structural Deck ScrewsLedger AttachmentGeneral PurposeConcreteTools & AccessoriesFastener ToolsCAMO Marksman ToolDeck ToolsPower ToolsLighting InstallationCable Railing InstallationPergola & PorchPergola SystemsLINXSimpson Strong-TieOZCOPergola Kits4x4 Kits6x6 Kits8x8 KitsPergola HardwarePergola Post BasesPergola Joist HangersPergola StrapsScreenSCREENEZE® Screen Frame Track SystemWestbury ScreenRailShop All ScreenColumnsVinyl ColumnsFaux Stone Column CoversAluminum Post and Column CoversPost AnchorsDeck LifePrivacy PanelsRDIDuraLifeDeck Railing AccessoriesTablesDog BowlsPlantersBird FeedersUmbrella HoldersDrink HoldersGrill Tool HoldersDrainageTrex RainEscapeZip-Up Under Deck DrainageUpSide Deck Ceiling by Color GuardDeck StainStain, Sealers & FinishesComposite Stains & Specialty StainsStain Preparation & ApplicationSale & Closeout Stain ProductsPost Sleeves & CoversPost SleevesVinyl Post Sleeves4x4 Aluminum Post Sleeves & Aluminum Post CoversFaux Stone Column WrapsStructural PostsDeck Gates & Metal Gate Hinges
